ebookdaily.com 2019-01-11

# eBookDaily - Free & Bargain Kindle Books. EVERY DAY!

### Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address or Facebook profile. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  1. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2. Improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  3. administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  4. To send periodic emails

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
FYI, we partner with the following sites and ad networks: 

  1. Facebook Developer API ([Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php))
  2. Google Adwords ([Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)) 
  3. Riot Ad Network ([Website](http://riotadnetwork.com/))

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to this privacy policy

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 6/9/2015
